mp3va.com 2015-04-24

# Mp3va.com - Privacy Policy

The privacy policy contains the information about the data which collected during the usage of the Mp3va.com (hereinafter referred to as the website).

Every user must register to get the access to the website services. The administration of the website reserves the right to make changes in the privacy policy without prior notification of its users. Therefor we advise you to check the conditions time to time to find out any changes or amendments.

#### Personal data

Personal data contains the following information which you provide during and after the registration: your valid email address, your first name, your last name, place of residence, age, sex, birthday, nickname, address, phone number etc. All the data is voluntarily provided and could be used for the website purposes (for example, the email address and the name could be used to contact the registered user), including for the obtaining the statistics which allow us to improve and update the website. We guarantee not to disclose your personal information to any third party and we guarantee you a full confidentiality when you're using the service provided by the website.

#### Financial information

All payment operations are made via a specially protected channel by protocol SSL (Secure Sockets Layer). The website does not collect your financial information and all the data including your credit card details or payment details are transferring directly to the processing centre which is responsible for the payment processing. The processing centre is not accessible to our service. Considering this you can be assured of the absolute reliability and security of the payments made with our website through the Internet.

#### Technical information

To provided the highest level of service to our customers we use "cookies". It's a small text file which help us to identify you on the next visit of the website. Cookies are not damaging your computer and cannot be used to destroy your hardware. If you like you can disable cookies in your browser. However in this case you will be logged out of your account at the website. We also use your IP-addresses in order to identify and get the statistics, which help us to improve the our service and to provide you the best service.

#### Responsibilities

The website does not undertakes the responsibility of the content and working capacity of the website or references which are located on the website. We also cannot guarantee that the provided in the help websites will be available and safe for your computer during your usage thereof. The user agrees not to pass his/her login and password to anyone else. The owner of a personal account bears all responsibility for damage caused as a result of passing the website login and password to a third persons.
